Guide to the Seattle Design Commission Project Files 1968-1986
Seattle Municipal Archives
- Seattle Design Commission Project Files, 1968-1986; 9323-02
  - 10th Avenue East / East Mercer (Widening) 7/15/71.9, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 8/58)
  - 1972 Green Triangle Program 8/26/71.11, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/59)
  - 5th Avenue North Widening 8/26/71.13, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 8/60)
  - 50th Avenue Northeast Widening 8/26/71.14, 1971 (Box-folder 8/61)
  - East Blaine Street Paving 8/26/71.15, 1971 (Box-folder 8/62)
  - Harvard Avenue East Widening 9/9/71.2, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 8/63)
  - Interbay Service Shops and Yards 9/23/71.2, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/64)
  - Rogers Park (Queen Anne Bowl) 9/23/71.3, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/65)
  - Seaview Avenue Northwest 9/23/71.5, 1971 (Box-folder 8/66)
  - 2nd Avenue Northwest / Streets Bounding Greenwood Playfield 10/7/71.2, 1971 (Box-folder 8/67)
  - Arterial Street Lighting Proposed Policy for Better Orientation 10/21/71.1, 1978 (Box-folder 8/68)
  - West Seattle Stadium 10/21/71.3, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 8/69)
  - Seward Park Access Revisions 10/21/71.6, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 8/70)
  - Alley in Block 13, North Seattle 11/4/71.2, 1971 (Box-folder 8/71)
  - Lincoln Park, Colman Pool 11/18/71.2, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 9/1)
  - 43rd Avenue South - Paving Improvements for Several Streets 11/18/71.5, 1971 (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Denny Way Street Improvements 12/2/71.1, 1971-1979 (Box-folder 9/3)
  - 6th Avenue South Paving 12/16/71.7, 1971 (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Private Development of Southeast Corner of Lake City Way Northeast and Northeast 125th Street 1/6/72.4, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Pedestrian Overpass, 23rd and East Jefferson Streets 1/6/72.6, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Northeast 42nd Street Improvements 1/6/72.7, 1972 (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Northwest 62nd Street / Ballard Recreation Center 1/20/72.5, 1972 (Box-folder 9/8)
  - 22nd Avenue Northwest Street Revisions 1/20/72.7, 1972 (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Commodore Park 2/17/72.2, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Atlantic City Boat Ramp 2/17/72.3, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Fire Station 31 3/2/72.2, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Thomas Park / Belmont Park 3/2/72.3, 1972 (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Phinney Ridge Playground (Woodland Park) 3/16/72.2, 1972 (Box-folder 9/14)
  - East Plaza Parking Garage 3/16/72.3, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Aurora Avenue North (Service Station Site) 3/16/72.4, 1972 (Box-folder 9/16)
  - West Lynn Place 3/16/72.5, 1972 (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Regional Place Training Center 3/16/72.8, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Seattle Center Improvements 4/6/72.1, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Harbor Patrol Helicopter Facilities / Lake Union 4/6/72.2, 1972 (Box-folder 9/20)
  - North Greenwood Storm Drains 4/6/72.3, 1972 (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Model Cities Funding Briefing 4/6/72.7, 1972 (Box-folder 9/22)
  - Fremont Bridge / Painting / Color Approval 4/20/72.2, 1972 (Box-folder 9/23)
  - South Bateman Street / Paving / Construction Drawings 4/20/72.5, 1972 (Box-folder 9/24)
  - 40th Avenue Northeast / Paving / Construction Drawings 4/20/72.6, 1972 (Box-folder 9/25)
  - Adams Neighborhood Improvement Program 5/18/72.1, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9/26)
  - South Connecticut Street 5/18/72.2, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9/27)
  - 33rd Avenue Northeast 5/18/72.4, 1972 (Box-folder 9/28)
  - 46th Avenue South 5/18/72.5, 1972 (Box-folder 9/29)
  - 1st and Seneca Mini-Park 5/18/72.10, 1972 (Box-folder 9/30)
  - Prefontaine Fountain Triangle Improvements 5/18/72.12, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9/31)
  - Pioneer Square Historic District / Street Lighting 5/18/72.13, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 9/32)
  - Model Cities Rehabilitation of Park Shelters 6/1/72.7, 1972 (Box-folder 9/33)
  - Low Impact Development Street Tree Proposals 6/1/72.10, 1972 (Box-folder 9/34)
  - South Rose Court 6/15/72.1, 1972 (Box-folder 9/35)
  - South Elmgrove Street 6/15/72.2, 1972 (Box-folder 9/36)
  - Northlake Urban Renewal Area / Street and Service Improvements 6/22/72.3, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 9/37)
  - Aurora Avenue North / 38th Street / 46th Street / Pedestrian Stairway and Landscaping 7/6/72.2, 1972 (Box-folder 9/38)
  - 38th Avenue Northeast / Paving 7/6/72.4, 1972 (Box-folder 9/39)
  - 49th Avenue South 7/6/72.5, 1972 (Box-folder 9/40)
  - East Republican Street Widening 7/6/72.6, 1972 (Box-folder 9/41)
  - Capitol Hill Traffic Diverters (Stevens Neighborhood) 7/6/72.9, 1972 (Box-folder 9/42)
  - Pike Project 7/6/72.10, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 9/43)
  - Yesler Terrace / Kobe Terrace Mini-Park 7/6/72.11, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 9/44)
  - Soundview Terrace Mini-Park 7/6/72.12, 1972 (Box-folder 9/45)
  - Sand Point Proposal Briefing 7/6/72.19, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 10/1)
  - Sand Point Proposal Briefing 7/6/72.19, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10/2)
  - Henderson Pumping Station 7/20/72.3, 1972 (Box-folder 10/3)
  - 41st Avenue Northeast 8/3/72.2, 1972 (Box-folder 10/4)
  - East-West Alley in Block 5 of Buckius Addition 8/3/72.3, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 10/5)
  - Aurora Avenue North / Street Tree Plantings 8/3/72.5, 1972 (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Hunter Boulevard South 8/17/72.3, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 10/7)
  - North 76th Street 8/17/72.4, 1972 (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Magnolia Playfield Lighting 8/17/72.7, 1972 (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Alki Avenue Development 8/17/72.11, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 10/10)
  - 36th Avenue Northwest 9/21/72.10, 1972 (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Ballard Avenue Northwest 9/21/72.11, 1972 (Box-folder 10/12)
  - 8th Avenue Northeast 9/21/72.12, 1972 (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Southwest Cambridge Street 9/21/72.13, 1972 (Box-folder 10/14)
  - Broadway Reservoir Lid 9/27/72.5, 1973 (Box-folder 10/15)
  - Broadway Reservoir Lid 9/27/72.5, 1972 (Box-folder 10/16)
  - Roy Street 9/27/72.8, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 10/17)
  - Seattle Center (Proposal for Completion and Redesign of International Fountain and Fountain Mall) 10/5/72.6, 1972 (Box-folder 10/18)
  - Haller Lake Parking Building 10/5/72.8, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 10/19)
  - Skybridges 10/19/72.10, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - South Park Recreation Center Rehabilitation 11/16/72.3, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Sealth Pool 11/16/72.4, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 10/22)
  - Brighton Shelterhouse Rehabilitation 11/16/72.7, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10/23)
  - Southwest Myrtle Street Stairway 12/7/72.4, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10/24)
  - Rockery Policies 12/7/72.6, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10/25)
  - Swedish Hospital Skybridge 12/7/72.14, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10/26)
  - 1973 Triangle Program 12/21/72.2, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10/27)
  - 40th Avenue South / Paving / Construction / South Eddy Street / Paving / Construction Drawings 12/21/72.4, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 10/28)
  - Spokane Street Bridges / West Waterway Pier Protection 12/21/72.5, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 10/29)
  - Project 27+ 1/4/73.2, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 10/30)
  - Project 27+ 1/4/73.2, 1973 (Box-folder 10/31)
  - East Waterway / South Bridge Replacement / Southwest Spokane Street 1/4/73.4, 1973 (Box-folder 10/32)
  - Laurelhurst Tiny Tot Playground 1/25/73.4, 1973-1983 (Box-folder 10/33)
  - Leschi Playground Development Street Tree Planting 1/25/73.8, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 10/34)
  - Pioneer Square Street Improvements 1/25/73.10, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 10/35)
  - Ballard Senior Citizens Service Center / Parking 1/25/73.11, 1973 (Box-folder 10/36)
  - 39th Avenue South / Concrete Walks 1/25/73.13, 1973 (Box-folder 10/37)
  - Ballard / Market Street Feasibility Study 1/25/73.15, 1973 (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Loyal Heights Pre-School Play Area 2/8/73.2, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Street Improvements 2/8/73.15, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 11/3)
  - Daybreak Star Indian Cultural Center 031573.9, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 11/4)
  - Daybreak Star Indian Cultural Center 031573.9, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 11/5)
  - 42nd Place South 4/5/73.9, 1973 (Box-folder 11/6)
  - 11th Avenue Southwest 4/5/73.10, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - East-West Alley in University District /4/5/73.11, 1973 (Box-folder 11/8)
  - Southwest Myrtle Street Stairs 4/5/73.13, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 11/9)
  - Northwest 57th Street 4/5/73.14, 1973 (Box-folder 11/10)
  - 28th Avenue 4/5/73.15, 1973 (Box-folder 11/11)
  - Magnolia Bridge Improvements 4/5/73.16, 1973 (Box-folder 11/12)
  - Holman Road Bridge Replacement 4/5/73.17, 1973 (Box-folder 11/13)
  - Volunteer Park Improvements 4/19/73.2 (Box-folder 11/14)
  - University District Street Trees 4/19/73.10 (Box-folder 11/15)
  - South Sullivan Street (8th Avenue South to West Marginal Way and 7 Alleys from 7th Avenue South to 12th Avenue South) - Paving 5/3/73.5, 1973 (Box-folder 11/16)
  - Fremont Projects 5/17/73.5, 1973 (Box-folder 11/17)
  - Ballard Tennis Courts 6/21/73.2, 1973 (Box-folder 11/18)
  - Licton Springs Park 6/21/73.3, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 11/19)
  - Camp Long Improvements 6/21/73.4, 1973-1980 (Box-folder 11/20)
  - Queen Anne Viewpoint 6/21/73.7, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 11/21)
  - Lincoln Reservoir Lid 6/21/73.8, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 11/22)
  - Lincoln Reservoir Lid 6/21/73.8, 1974 (Box-folder 11/23)
  - Lincoln Reservoir Lid 6/21/73.8, 1973 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Skybridge to Monorail Station 6/21/73.10, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Northeast Queen Anne Viewpoint 7/12/73.13, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - North 45th Street Bridge Improvements 7/26/73.2, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Boyd Place Southwest - Retaining Walls 7/26/73.3, 1973 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Yesler Way Bridges 7/26/73.5, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - On-Call Consultants 7/26/73.6, 1973 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Yesler Way Retaining Wall / Designer Selection 8/9/73.6, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - West Seattle Freeway (Existing) Median Barrier 8/9/73.7, 1973 (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Northeast 100th Street / Paving, etc. 8/9/73.8, 1973 (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Alley, Block 15, South Park Addition / Paving 8/9/73.9, 1973 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Roy Street Signing 9/6/73.5, 1973 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - 42nd Avenue South / Curb and Gutter 10/4/73.3, 1973 (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Alley Block 14, Mercer's Addition to North Seattle 10/4/73.4, 1973 (Box-folder 12/14)
  - 7th Avenue / Walks and Other Improvements 10/4/73.5, 1973 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Elliott Bay Park / Myrtle Edwards 11/1/73.5, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - South Service Center 11/01/73.6, 1973 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Northwest 57th Street / Street Trees 11/01/73.9, 1973 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - North Bowdoin Place 11/15/73.4, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Fremont Street Tree Planting Program / Phases I, II, and III 111573.5, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - Broadview Branch Library 12/13/73.7, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - Holman Road Northwest / Widening / Briefing 12/13/73.8, 1973 (Box-folder 12/22)
  - 5th Avenue South 121373.9, 1973 (Box-folder 12/23)
  - 4th Avenue South 1/17/74.7, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 12/24)
  - F. A. C. E. Street Trees 011774.12, 1974 (Box-folder 12/25)
  - Southwest Roxbury - Unit "C" 1/17/74.13, 1974 (Box-folder 12/26)
  - Delridge Way Southwest 1/17/74.14, 1974 (Box-folder 12/27)
  - Transmission Line / South Substation to East Pine 1/17/74.15, 1974 (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Yesler Way Bridges over 4th and 5th Avenues 2/21/74.3, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 12/29)
  - 39th Avenue Northeast - Paving, etc. 2/21/74.5, 1974 (Box-folder 12/30)
  - South Park NDP, Street Trees 022174.11, 1974 (Box-folder 12/31)
  - Green Lake Boating and Sailing Facility 3/07/74.5, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 12/32)
  - South College Street Park 3/07/74.6, 1974 (Box-folder 12/33)
  - CBD Exclusive Transit Lanes and Amenities Boulevard 3/21/74.4, 1974 (Box-folder 12/34)
  - Northwest Market Street 3/21/74.5, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 12/35)
  - Pike Project 022174.13, 1976 (Box-folder 12/36)
  - Pike Project 022174.13, 1975 (Box-folder 12/37)
  - Pike Project 022174.13, 1974 (Box-folder 12/38)
  - Dallas Avenue South 3/21/74.8, 1974 (Box-folder 12/39)
  - One Percent for Art 040474.5, 1974 (Box-folder 12/40)
  - South Washington Street 04/11/74.1, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 12/41)
  - Burlington - Northern Trail 5/2/74.3, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 12/42)
  - Pacific Street - Northeast and North 5/2/74.7, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Pacific Street - Northeast and North 5/2/74.7, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Tilikum Place 5/02/74.8, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Lake City Way Northeast Underground 5/02/74.10, 1974 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Northlake Bikeway 5/02/74.11, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Pike Street UAB 5/16/74.4, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Alley in Block 9, Madrona Park Addition 5/16/74.5, 1974 (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Montlake Boulevard / Arterial Underground 5/16/74.7, 1974 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Hiawatha Playfield Lighting 6/13/74.8, 1974 (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Queen Anne Pool 6/13/74.11, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 13/10)
  - Carkeek Park 6/13/74.12, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 13/11)
  - Capitol Hill View Point 6/13/74.13, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13/12)
  - Fauntleroy Avenue Center Cuts 6/13/74.14, 1974 (Box-folder 13/13)
  - Lincoln Park Improvements 6/27/74.9, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 13/14)
  - Alley in Block 1 of Day's Park Addition 07/18/74.2, 1974 (Box-folder 13/15)
  - Cowen Park Improvements 07/18/74.8, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Central Area Playfield 07/18/74.9, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 13/17)
  - 34th Street and Pike Street - Mini-Park 07/18/74.10, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 13/18)
  - Golden Gardens Park Improvements 07/18/74.11, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13/19)
  - Fire Station 24 07/18/74.12, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 13/20)
  - Animal Control Facility 07/18/74.13, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 13/21)
  - Haller Lake Site View Study 07/18/74.14, 1974 (Box-folder 13/22)
  - Green Lake Concession Building (Recreation Center) 8/08/74.6, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 13/23)
  - Public Safety Building 08/08/74.9, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 13/24)
  - South Holden Street 08/08/74.10, 1974 (Box-folder 13/25)
  - 16th Avenue Southwest 08/08/74.11, 1974 (Box-folder 13/26)
  - Bus Shelter Program 8/22/74.3, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 13/27)
  - Bus Shelter Program 8/22/74.3, 1975 (Box-folder 13/28)
  - Bus Shelter Program 8/22/74.3, 1974 (Box-folder 13/29)
  - Pike Project / Corner Market Rehabilitation 090574.1, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Curb Cuts 092674.2, 1974 (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Bus Stop Sign Replacements 092674.8, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 14/3)
  - 20th Avenue South 092674.12, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Westlake Monorail / Protection Shields 092674.13, 1974 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - South Raymond Street 100374.1, 1974 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Burke Gilman Trail - Coast Guard Site 102474.1 / 071979.6 D, 1978-1983 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Burke Gilman Trail - Coast Guard Site 102474.1 / 071979.6 D, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Burke Gilman Trail - Coast Guard Site 102474.1 / 071979.6 D, 1981 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Burke Gilman Trail - Coast Guard Site 102474.1 / 071979.6 D, 1980 (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Burke Gilman Trail - Coast Guard Site 102474.1 / 071979.6 D (Box-folder 14/11)
  - University Distrcit Skybridge 102474.2, 1974 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - Van Asselt Community Center Improvements 102474.4, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 14/13)
  - Burke Gilman Trail / Burke Gilman Place Park 102474.7, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 14/14)
  - Burke Gilman Trail / Master Plan 102474.7, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 14/15)
  - 1974 Green Triangle Program 102474.11 (Box-folder 14/16)
  - South Substation to East Pine Street 111774.15, 1972 (Box-folder 14/17)
  - Sand Point Way Northeast 121274.1, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 14/18)
  - 3rd Avenue South 121274.3, 1974 (Box-folder 14/19)
  - 5th Avenue Central Business District Street Improvement 121274.5, 1976 (Box-folder 14/20)
  - 5th Avenue Central Business District Street Improvement 121274.5, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 14/21)
  - Olive Street / Curb Setbacks 121274.6, 1974 (Box-folder 14/22)
  - Beacon Avenue South Street Trees 011675.0, 1975 (Box-folder 15/1)
  - West Howe Street Bridge Repair 011675.10, 1975 (Box-folder 15/2)
  - Alley in Block 15 of Rainier Beach Addition 11675.12, 1975 (Box-folder 15/3)
  - 8th Avenue North 011675.8, 1975 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Alley Between Blocks 45 and 46 011675.17, 1974 (Box-folder 15/5)
  - 38th Avenue South 2/6/75.1, 1975 (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Alaskan Way Ferry Destination Signing 2/6/75.2, 1975 (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Woodland Park Zoo / Jones Master Plan 020675.5, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Ballard Circle Park 2/6/75.8, 1975 (Box-folder 15/9)
  - West Seattle Reservoir Park 2/6/75.9, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Seattle Tennis Center 2/6/75.10, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Seattle Tennis Center 2/6/75.10, 1975 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Seattle Tennis Center 2/6/75.10, 1974 (Box-folder 15/13)
  - South Eddy Street to 40th Avenue South 022075.2, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 15/14)
  - 6th Avenue and Lenora Street Skybridge (Private) 022075.9, 1975 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - Montlake Community Center 030675.8, 1975 (Box-folder 15/16)
  - Alki Avenue Southwest 030675.15, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 15/17)
  - Westlake Avenue North Wire Undergrounding 030675.16, 1975 (Box-folder 15/18)
  - View Ridge Reservoir and Pump Station 032075.1, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Park Standards 032075.6, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 16/2)
  - 15th Avenue East 032675.4, 1975 (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Alaskan Way South 040375.1, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Magnolia Playfield 041775.3, 1975 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Fremont Neighborhood Improvement Program 041775.7, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Lake Union Access 041775.9, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Viewland Receiving Station 041775.10, 1976 (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Viewland Receiving Station 041775.10, 1975 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Viewland Receiving Station 041775.10, 1974 (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Spokane Street 050175.2, 1975 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - 22nd Avenue Northwest 050175.6, 1975 (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Solid Waste Ammonia Project 052076.7, 1977 (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Solid Waste Ammonia Project 052076.7, 1976 (Box-folder 16/14)
  - Solid Waste Ammonia Project 052076.7, 1975 (Box-folder 16/15)
  - Discovery Park Neighborhood Playground Improvements 060575.3 (032769.7), 1975 (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Brighton Playground 060575.7, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Bonair Drive Southwest 060575.13, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Meridian Playground 061975.2, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Harbor Tours / Pier 56 Concrete Ballustrade 061975.4 (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Pike Project Hillclimb Corridor 061975.7, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 17/6)
  - Central West Seattle Playfield 070375.2, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 17/7)
  - Central West Seattle Playfield 070375.2, 1975 (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Rainier Avenue South 071775.2, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Rainier Street Trees / Madrona Neighborhood Improvement Program Street Trees / Stevens Neighborhood Improvement Program Street Trees 071775.3 / 071775.4 / 071775.5, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - South King Street 080775.2, 1975 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - East to West Alley, Block 10 080775.3, 1975 (Box-folder 17/12)
  - 4th Avenue Northwest and 5th Avenue Northwest - Repaving 080775.4, 1975 (Box-folder 17/13)
  - 1975 Green Triangle / Roosevelt Way and 143rd Street North 080775.7 (Box-folder 17/14)
  - East Republican Street (15th Avenue East, East Aloha Street, 19th Avenue East, and East Thomas Street), by Traffic Diverter 080775.10, 1975 (Box-folder 17/15)
  - International District Streetscaping 082175.1, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 17/16)
  - Washington Street Triangle 082175.8, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17/17)
  - Discovery Park - Roadway 090475.3, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 17/18)
  - Opera House (Lighting) 091175.1, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 17/19)
  - Genesee Park 091175.6, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 17/20)
  - Genesee Park 091175.6, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17/21)
  - Building Signing vs. Artwork 091875.6, 1975 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - Pedestrian Overpass Study 091875.9, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - Alley Bridge - Seattle Trust and Savings Bank 100275.2, 1975 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - South Holgate Street and 1st Avenue South 100275.3, 1975 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Yesler / Lakewood Addition / Paving North to South Alley, Block 3 100275.4, 1975 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - East Harrison Street 100275.5, 1975 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Pier 59 (Aquarium / Waterfront Park) 100275.6, 1971-1976 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Neighborhood Traffic Diverters Stevens and Brighton 101675.1, 1975 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Alley, Block 4 Paving, etc. 101675.3, 1975 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Leschi Neighborhood Improvement Program - Stairway Lighting 101675.7, 1975 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Hing Hay Park / Information Kiosk 101675.10, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Woodland Park Zoo / Commissary 110675.2, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Alley, Block 4, Walla Walla 110675.8, 1975 (Box-folder 18/13)
  - Albion Place North 110675.9, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Yesler / Atlantic Park and Recreation Center 112075.6, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Occidental Mall Extension 112075.10, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 18/16)
  - University Way Crosswalks 112075.11, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 18/17)
  - Seattle Center / Maintenance Levy 112075.12, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 18/18)
  - Northwest 87th Street / 15th Avenue Northwest 120475.3, 1975 (Box-folder 18/19)
  - Railing Replacement - 15th Avenue Northwest and Magnolia Bridge 121875.8 / 121875.9, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 18/20)
  - Ornamental Pedestrian Lighting 011576.7, 1976 (Box-folder 18/21)
  - 34th Street and Union Street Pedestrian Improvements 011576.8, 1976 (Box-folder 18/22)
  - Ballard Avenue Street Improvements 011576.9, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 18/23)
  - Ballard Avenue Street Improvements 011576.9, 1976 (Box-folder 18/24)
  - Montlake Bridge / Color Selection 020576.1, 1976 (Box-folder 18/25)
  - Sunrise House Alterations 020576.6, 1976 (Box-folder 18/26)
  - 8th Avenue Southwest 020576.9, 1976 (Box-folder 18/27)
  - Alley, Block 22 020576.12, 1976 (Box-folder 18/28)
  - Neighborhood Improvement Programs 020576.14, 1980 (Box-folder 18/29)
  - Central Metro Transit Facility 021976.3 (Box-folder 18/30)
  - Skybridge / Nordstrom 021976.5 (Box-folder 18/31)
  - Marion Street Pedestrian Bridge - Type, Size, and Location Study 021976.7, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 18/32)
  - Brooklyn Avenue Northeast 021976.9 (Box-folder 18/33)
  - Horton Hill Corridor 030476.2, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 18/34)
  - Discovery Park Buffer Planting 030476.3, 1976 (Box-folder 18/35)
  - Greenwood Business District Low Impact Development (North 83rd Street and North 90th Street) 030476.5, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 18/36)
  - Bikeways 031876.1, 1980-1983 (Box-folder 18/37)
  - Bikeways 031876.1, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 18/38)
  - Bikeways 031876.1, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 18/39)
  - 13th Avenue West and West Gilman Street 031876.9, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 18/40)
  - Seneca Street Tree Planting 031876.12, 1976 (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Pike Place Market Sidewalk, Street and Alley Improvements 040176.1, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Alaskan Way Street Car 041576.2, 1976 (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Alley Block 3 Ashford Addition Paving 041576.5, 1976 (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Alley Block 2 Buckius Addition Paving 041576.6, 1976 (Box-folder 19/5)
  - Safety Signals Phase I 8th Avenue and James Street 041576.7, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Alley Block 19 Hill Tract Addition Paving 041576.9, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 19/7)
  - 20th Avenue Northeast Bridge - Bicycle and Pedestrian Improvements 041576.10, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Leschi Neighborhood Improvement Program Area 041576.11, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 19/9)
  - California Avenue Southwest Street Trees / Atlantic Neighborhood Improvement Program Street Trees / First Hill Neighborhood Improvement Program Street Trees 041576.12 / 041576.13 / 041576.14, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 19/10)
  - Courtyard Exhibition Hall 041576.16, 1976 (Box-folder 19/11)
  - Victory Heights Playground 050676.6, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 19/12)
  - North 45th Street Trees 061776.6, 1976 (Box-folder 19/13)
  - Bryant Neighborhood Playground 061776.9, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 19/14)
  - Schmitz Waterfront Park 061776.10, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 19/15)